Svitlyachok — a Ukrainian platform for preserving childhood memories
The public feed is open to everyone — no account needed
Filtering memories by topic and city, sorting by new or popular
A full memory page — likes and comments ask visitors to sign in first
Creating an account — name, email, password
The personal archive — empty for a brand-new user
Creating a recipe memory: type, city, topic, title, story, ingredients, steps
Uploading a photo and saving — the memory is published
The saved memory: photo, story, ingredients and cooking steps
Memories can be edited — changing the title
Dashboard filters: all / public / private memories
Community: opening another member's memory
Sending Warmth — the platform's gentle take on a like
Leaving a comment
Reporting content to the moderators
Lost Fireflies — requests to find lost photos, classmates, places
Posting a request: city, place type, years, what to look for, contact email
The published request — full description and a contact button
Editing the profile — name, bio, avatar
Logging out — and switching to the admin's side of the story
The admin panel — the report we just sent is in the queue
Admins can remove reported content
User management — ban and unban
Community rules — kind, calm, Ukrainian-first
About the project
Svitlyachok — keep the light of your childhood